http://www.cmymorgans.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home »
Effective date: January 26, 2019
cmymorgans (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the http://www.cmymorgans.com website (the “Service”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. Our Privacy Policy for cmymorgans is created with the help of the Free Privacy Policy website.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from http://www.cmymorgans.com
Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
First name and last name
Phone number
Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
cmymorgans uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain the Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer care and support
To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
To monitor the usage of the Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
cmymorgans will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure Of Data
Legal Requirements
cmymorgans may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of cmymorgans
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By visiting this page on our website: www.cmymorgans.com
Recent Posts
Looking for the Quality CBD Items
Why Go Solar in 2018-Benefits of Solar Energy
Why Having Trees in Your Property is a Good Idea
6 Bathroom Remodeling Ideas
The Most Common Dangerous Pests in a House
Search for:
Recent Comments
RSS FEEDLooking for the Quality CBD Items June 29, 2020You might be feeling confused of the items that you could see online especially if you are not so sure if this one is branded or not since that there are many people and sellers who will sell fake items and things on the internet. It is hard to find and look for the best […] secure_adminWhy Go Solar in 2018-Benefits of Solar Energy March 9, 2020The most common reason why homeowners switch to solar is to cut their energy costs. Aside from the fact that it’s also nature friendly, solar panel is a great energy source if you want an efficiency upgrade. It is a great way to improve property value and reduce carbon footprint. If you want to install […] secure_adminWhy Having Trees in Your Property is a Good Idea July 19, 2019Trees in the property can go two different ways for you, they could be something amazing or it could turn out problematic for you. If you want to avoid that you can always make sure to hire charlotte tree service for the maintenance of your trees. When you make sure that the trees in your properties are […] secure_admin6 Bathroom Remodeling Ideas February 3, 2019If your fixtures and features are outdated, it’s now time to rethink about having your bathroom remodeled. There are lots of modern features that can install in your bathroom to make it look like how you want it. According to companies of home repair in Lubbock that are expert in bathroom remodeling, homeowners want to have their bathroom […] secure_adminThe Most Common Dangerous Pests in a House May 20, 2018The pests in our home are not just ugly looking critters that are fond of chewing your wiring. A lot of them can actually cause serious health issues for you and your family. In this article, you will learn some of the most common house pests that possibly live in your home and can cause serious health […] secure_adminHow to Make Sure that Your Garage Door is Secured While on Vacation March 24, 2018Keeping the security and safety of your house is definitely on top of your priority list. However, while you take care to ensure that you look at your windows and doors when you leave for vacation, it is also very important that you ensure that your garage door is properly secured against any potential intruders.  […] secure_admin Archives
June 2020
March 2020
July 2019
February 2019
May 2018
March 2018
Categories
CBD Services
